New York City's new job center. The line to get in. All these people hoping to get a job
with the city. About 2,500 people went.
The line was endless. As you can see, it keeps on going and going. All this is looking for
a job with the city. This is insane. It shows you how messed up things are right now in the world.
[Reading a post] "I'll save you the trouble as someone who went on opening day today: they started turning people away after noon. Once I made it a bit further up the line..."
"...I learned they're not currently hiring anyone or accepting resumes. They're only helping people apply on the city jobs website."
This is when they started turning people away.
This is not on any media sites as well. These are the videos I'm seeing online from people recording their experiences.
The Mayor's office did text me about this opening, and I did go, but it was closed that day, and it was warned that it will get crazy on opening day.
But these are all people trying to find a job, particularly with the City of New York.
This is nuts. This shows you how rough it is to find a job in New York. Look how long that line is.